<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>01 All aboard</title>
      <link>/post/all-aboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/all-aboard/</guid>
      <description>Fleep is the new tinder for data scientists. After some online speed dataing a team was born. I showed my wife a list of names we&amp;rsquo;d come up with. The result of the vote is at the end of this post. Sorry Fleep, once we got serious it was time for Slack where we set up a channel called let&amp;rsquo;s do for voting using emojis. It&amp;rsquo;s a good way to keep trigger happy channel creators under control 😊.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>04 ABS workout</title>
      <link>/post/04-abs-workout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/04-abs-workout/</guid>
      <description>Are you tough enough for this journey? Want stronger ABS? We added census data-packs to our lanky Data2App by visiting the 2016 Australian Bureau of Statistics data packs website.
It’s like a candy store for data geeks. We picked four flavours
Plum AgeBlueberry StudentsMint IncomeMarmalade EmploymentWith these new flavours, users of our Data2App can cherry pick their stops according to passengers from neighbourhoods with above average age, higher proportions of students, higher income or higher rate of employment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>03 Next stop Data2App</title>
      <link>/post/03-next-stop-data2app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/03-next-stop-data2app/</guid>
      <description>Freebies are tempting. We considered using the free for a limited time Tableau. In my opinion though, R Shiny has three things that shone through
wealth of community packagesfree for an unlimited timerequires knowledge of R and codingPerhaps some people think the last point is a drawback - horses for courses. There’s a more in depth comparison on homeagency
This was our first version on shinyapps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>02 Window seat</title>
      <link>/post/window-seat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/window-seat/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a lot easier driving when you&amp;rsquo;re looking out the windscreen to see where you&amp;rsquo;re going. Two members of the Mathemagicians had previous experience and their advice was our windscreen.
 Data ingestion was a challenge
 The main recurring theme of the best team projects was that they found a clear and coherent problem to solve and they focused on it
 I can’t emphasise enough how important research into the industry is</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a competitor in this year&amp;rsquo;s (2018) Melbourne Datathon in a team of five. We&amp;rsquo;re called the Mathemagicians and are a mixed bunch of students and professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>